MICHAEL ORDETX

1343 Hancock Street, Tallahassee, FL 32304 · (941)-993-2413

Email Address · LinkedIn Profile

A driven learner with strong entrepreneurial ambition who has earned a B.S. in Finance from Florida State University and is currently studying and pursuing a degree in the school's Graduate MBA Program.

Particularly experienced and knowledgeable regarding Customer Service, Data Analysis, Office-Suite Related skills, Public Speaking, Strategic Planning, Social Media Analytics, and Web Design.

EDUCATION

JUNE 2021

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN FINANCE, FLORIDA STATE UNIVERSITY

- 2.88 Overall GPA
- 3.22 Upper-Level GPA
- Dean's List Award Recipient

RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNE 2020 – AUGUST 2020

WEBSITE DESIGN CONSULTANT, SHADOWBROOK INVESTMENTS, LLC

- Redesigned website from the ground up for a subsidiary company of Shadowbrook
- Worked with employees of the company to get suggestions for curated site features
- Utilized a blend of Squarespace and Javascript to build the ideal website for the client

JUNE 2017 – AUGUST 2021

STEM PROGRAM ASSISTANT, PINNACLE ACADEMY, INC. – LAKEWOOD RANCH, FL

- Helped create curriculum for a variety of educational summer programs
- Co-supervised programs with faculty at Pinnacle Academy, expressing maturity and patience when working with students with special needs

MAY 2017

FINANCE/MARKETING INTERN, HUMBLE.TV – NEW YORK CITY, NY

- First work experience relating to finance as a career path and major choice
- Worked on financial planning and fund allocation for various ad campaigns
- Opportunity to speak/work with executive members of large companies such as UPS

APRIL 2016 – JANUARY 2017

SERVER/CASHIER, FAST N FRESH - LAKEWOOD RANCH, FL

- First substantial experience in terms of career development and interacting with employers and customers alike
- Gained numerous skills regarding customer service and personal presentation in the workplace, such as making on the spot decisions and managing time properly